associate-o-matic.com 2019-05-20

# Associate-O-Matic | Privacy Policy

****

At Associate-O-Matic we are heavily committed to your privacy. We despise spam. Maintaining the privacy and integrity of your account is of paramount importance to us. If you would like to see our privacy policy include something else, then please get in contact with us.

**Security**  
Associate-O-Matic has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information. We take stringent precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. We do not sell or give away information obtained from customers and prospective customers. 

**Notice**  
To customize our site to your needs, we will initiate a one time only request for information from you when you attempt to access a customizable section of our web site. Such data will enable us to identify you each time you enter our site and provides us with some marketing demographic data. This information is provided through a User Profile when you first attempt to download freeware or trialware, subscribe to e-mail newsletters or sign up for field testing. We utilize your personal information for these three purposes:

\- To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.   
\- To help us create content most relevant to you.   
\- To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Gyrofly. 

**Consent**  
If you decide to register or provide personal information, you will be able to select the types of information you want to receive from Associate-O-Matic. If you do not want Associate-O-Matic to communicate with you about other offers regarding Associate-O-Matic products, new software, events, or services by e-mail, postal mail or telephone, you may deselect the appropriate option.

**Access**  
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the User Profile page. There you can:

\- View and edit personal information you have already given us.   
\- Tell us whether you want Associate-O-Matic to send you marketing information.   
\- Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products.   
\- Register. Once you register, you won't need to do it again.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**Enforcement**  
If for some reason you believe Associate-O-Matic has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at [**support@associate-o-matic.com**](mailto:support@associate-o-matic.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain that the words Privacy Policy are in the subject line.
